yemenhr.com 2010-06-14

# Yemen HR - Jobs in Yemen: Privacy Policy

****

Our privacy policy states that: “ _We will not collect any of your personal information unless you agree to provide them as requested in our forms. We will not disseminate your information to a third party unless it is permitted by you and only for the sake of job matching.  We will not sell, or share your personal information with any other third party outside the scope of our terms and conditions whatsoever_”

As a part of our goals to improve this website and monitor its use, we usually collect some technical information that help us determine who and how many users are visiting our website. Such information include IP addresses, type of browsers, operating systems...Etc. We do not identify you personally throughout the collection of this information. We collect this information because we aggregate it to improve the performance of our website.

We use what is called “Session cookies” to help you interact with our website more effectively. Such cookies are deleted as soon as you close the browser. The use of “session cookies” does not unveil your identity; it just help you move around the website while you are logged in and help save you time of typing several information into different pages. The uses of these cookies is mandatory for our system and are not violating your privacy.

We use the email you provide with your subscription to contact you in case of opportunities and when needed. We also use it to update you with the latest of our website. You can choose to unsubscribe at any moment. We do not share our email list with any third party whatsoever. We respect your privacy and we are keen to keep you safe.

Sometimes, we put links to other external websites; such websites are not part of our privacy policy or terms of use. They have their own policies and terms that you should read before usage.

We are committed to the privacy of our users and we will do our best to maintain all your personal information in a safe place and only accessible after your permission. Please contact us if you have any question or concern.
